sis.com 2017-10-30

# Silicon Integrated Systems(SiS) -Privacy Policy

This privacy policy express the how the information collected from this web site will be used. If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please contact us at _pims@sis.com_

**Information Collected**

You do not have to provide any personal information to use this web site, submitting personal information is voluntary. However, when you submitting personal Information (such as your name, mailing address, email address and other contact information) it constitutes your consent to the use of such information for the purpose(s) stated below.

**Use of Information Collected**

The personal information collected is used to respond to your inquiries that you request. The information collected is also used to help us to upgrade the quality of our website and the services that we provide over the website. 

We reserve the right to provide such personal information to our officers, employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to execute certain web services (such as web hosting or maintenance services) for us. We also reserve the right to disclose such information to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following: (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect or prosecute criminal offences or attacks on the technical integrity of the web site or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, the users of the website, or the public.

**Update Your Personal Information**

Your personal information collected from this web site will be properly saved and reserved in the website database for six months. You may ask us to update or delete such information anytime during such six-month period. You may do so by sending email to the following address: _pims@sis.com_ .

**Web Traffic-related Information**

Our web server automatically records certain information incidental to your use of our website, such as the name of your IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that you use, and other similar web-traffic information. Information regarding your and other visitors' traffic patterns may be aggregated to compile a web transaction report to show various web traffic-related information, but in no event that any individual’s web traffic-related information, including yours, will be used respectively for any purpose.

**Revisions to Our Privacy Policy**

SiS reserves the right to revise this privacy policy at any time. You may ascertain if our privacy policy has been so revised by referring to the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of this page. Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this privacy policy as revised by us, and you should therefore review this privacy policy regularly to ensure that you know of its terms.

Last Updated @ October, 2012
